McKersie, Robert B., Files /4033
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Alcon Industries Ltd. Reorganization Agreement 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- "Industrial Society" Magazine Nov., Dec, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- British News Clippings, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- EEF (Box 6, Folder 11)
- EEF, Otis, McNeill, Gullick, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Industrial Relations, A Basic Book List (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Mobile Oil Company, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- ETU, TGWU, Rubber, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Report on Labor Relations- G. Liddle, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- National Board for Prices and Incomes Productivity Agreements Evaluation Reference, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Fourteen House Clerical Agreement, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Schedule of the incentive Scheme in Operation at Tudor House, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- International Printers Ltd., British Federation of Master Printers, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- International Publishing Corporation Ltd. And Society of Graphical and Allied Trades, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- The Daily Mirror Newspapers Limited, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Chemical ICI, CIA, Phil Black, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Shell U.K. Ltd., 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Mobile Oil Company Ltd. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- First World Congress International Industrial Relations Association: The Significance of Productivity Bargaining/ L' Importance Des Negociations Collectives Relatives A La Productivite, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  French Language
- The Electricity Council, National Joint Industrial Council for the Electricity Supply Industry, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Kraft Foods Ltd., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- National Graphical Association, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Piecework Wage Determination in Coventry- William Brown, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Comments on P&G, interview with Robert Tanner (Armour & Company), Notes on British Trip, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Study on Class Stratification in Modern Britain, Macmillan Notes for Authors, Code of Industrial Relations Practice, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Number in Training by Type of Training, Sex, Ethnic Characteristics, and Sic, Wage Study and Industry Variables Used in Regression (Box 7, Folder 11)
- B+ B Bargaining Exercise (Box 7, Folder 12)
- "The Locus of Decision Making," "The Origin and Meaning of Work Rules," "The Pilkington Story" (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Thomson Newspapers, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Filing Notes and Minutes of Meetings of Joint Modernisation Committees, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Productivity Agreement Between London Ocean Trades Employers' Association Ltd. And the Dockworkers, London Riverside Productivity Agreement 1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- BP Chemicals U.K., 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Docks, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Ford Motor Company Ltd., 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- B.R.B., Shell U.K. Ltd., BP Chemical and Other Miscellaneous Papers (Box 7, Folder 20)